Favour Asuk



favourasuk@gmail.com



09019430948, 08111406834



linkedin.com/in/favour-asuk-27b336204



https://github.com/AsukFavour

Summary

A software engineering professional with experience specializing in software development, computer science.HTML, Design, CSS, React Js, Python, JavaScript, Angular Js. A proven record of accomplishment for executing complex technical projects for the development of efficient applications.

Experience



Software Engineer

Freelance (Self employed)

- development of an e-commerce web app for a furniture brand
- management of the web applications

Software Engineer

Advantec Security Solutions Ltd (NYSC)

Jan 2023 - Jun 2023 (6 months)

- Contributed to the development and management of software
- Collaborated with various developers
- -Attended meetings and gave resourceful contributions

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROJECT

Afe Babalola University

Sep 2018 - Jul 2022 (3 years 11 months)

Designed, developed, built a web application for web devices to aid customers have a better experience when shopping online by providing them with a 3-Deminsional object of their desired item which included application testing, designing and code creating using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Web Designer intern

MR-soft International

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021 (7 months)

Coordinate with the software engineering team to develop custom for enterprise customers, including

- . performing debugging activities and providing meaningful recommendations to improve user functionality
- . Performed testing and development for web application in HTML, JavaScript, Anjular Js.
- . Attended meetings with the project team to identity potential risk, resolve project roadblocks, and ensure compliance with user specifications and requirements

Education



Afe Babalola University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

2018 - 2022

I obtained a B.Sc in computer science with Second Class Upper Honors. i i acquired knowledge in both the theoretical and technical aspect of computer science.

Licenses & Certifications



糞 graduate member - Computer Professionals Registration Council of Nigeria

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • HTML5 • Web Development • Web Design • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • AngularJS • GitHub • React.js